<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RollinBass</string>
    <string name="logo_description">RollinBass principal logo</string>
    <string name="mail">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="new_acc">" Still not registered? Create a new account."</string>
    <string name="user">User name</string>
    <string name="nombre">Name and Lastname</string>
    <string name="fecha_nacimiento">Roll in Bass</string>
    <string name="register">Sign up</string>
    <string name="promotora">Promoter</string>
    <string name="djs">Djs</string>
    <string name="test">test</string>
    <string name="eventos">Events</string>
    <string name="intro_logos">"Hey Family!🎉🙌🔥🔥\n\nWe would like to give a little explanation about our designs and logos. What do they mean? Where they come from?: "</string>
    <string name="logos">Logos</string>
    <string name="foto_familia">Family picture</string>
    <string name="logo_bellota">Acorn logo</string>
    <string name="logo_abubilla">Abubilla logo</string>
    <string name="texto_bellota">Why the Acorn?🌰\nIt represents the project birth, an Illusion. A way to go.</string>
    <string name="texto_abubilla">Why the Abubilla?🐦\nIt\'s an extension of us, our link with the nature and animal conscious. This our wildest side and at the same the time the most responsible one.</string>
    <string name="logo_encina">Holm oak logo</string>
    <string name="texto_encina">Why the Holm Oak?🌳\nIt\'s the Family, roots and our sign of identity. Perfect photonsyntesis between our dreams and the RollinPeople.</string>
    <string name="pie_logos">This would not have been possible without our designers @gloevolutionsoccer and @drty.dsgn.\nThank you for bringing life and color to all our crazy things.\n\nThanks a million for bringing us to life!\n\n# RollinPeople</string>
    <string name="ig_rollinBass">\@rollinbass</string>
    <string name="ig_gloevolutionsoccer">\@gloevolutionsoccer</string>
    <string name="ig_drty.dsgn">\@drty.dsgn</string>
    <string name="nombre_artista_hint">Artist name</string>
    <string name="alias">Nickname</string>
    <string name="genero_musical">Musical genre</string>
    <string name="descripcion_dj">Dj description</string>
    <string name="identidad">Identity</string>
    <string name="video_pausado">Video pause</string>
    <string name="reproducciendo">Playing video</string>
    <string name="bienvenida">Welcome to RollinPage</string>
    <string name="info_video">Click on the video to play it</string>
    <string name="generos_musicales">Musical genres</string>
    <string name="biografia">Biography</string>
    <string name="registro_exito">Succesfull sing up</string>
    <string name="artistas">Artists</string>
    <string name="usuario">User</string>
    <string name="error_usuario_no_existente">The user does not exist in our database. Make sure you are entering it correctly or sign up if you are not. :)</string>
    <string name="error_mail">No valid mail</string>
    <string name="error_pass">ERROR!!! Incorrect password.</string>
    <string name="error_campo_vacio">This field cannot be incomplete</string>
    <string name="pagina_registro">Sign up! :)</string>
    <string name="rollin_history">Roll in Bass is a reality that is born from the illusion of a family.🙂\n\nEach of us has grown hand in hand with drum and bass, break and dubstep music. In love with the broken rhythms and their BPM. When we talk about a team, we talk about a group, and when we talk about a group, illusions, goals and objectives come into play.\nA family.❤❤\n\nIt is said that when a person is constant and has a goal, in one way or another, sooner or later he will achieve it as a result of work. Now we want to achieve that goal among all of us. We would like to share with everyone our vision and the BPM we beat at all the volume we can.\nWe will be accompanied by local artists, from the land, young and with origin denomination. Both national and international, bringing novelty and freshness to the scene, promoting it hand in hand with all these artists.🎧🎵\n\nSEE YOU AT THE SOUNDSYSTEM🔥🙌🔥🙌!!\n\n\nConnect to #RollinPeople:</string>
    <string name="eventos_problem">"NOTICE OF TEMPORARY SUSPENSION OF EVENTS:\n\n\nDue to the current situation and the measures taken in the party and event places by the different administrations to prevent the spread of the virus, we communicate the suspension of events until the situation improves and We can offer a service according to the level we want to give.\n\nSending you strength and encouragement to overcome these difficult times.❤ 🎧 "</string>
    <string name="error_usuario_existente">ERROR!!\nThe user already exists, enter a new one</string>
    <string name="error">ERROR!!</string>
    <string name="error_campos_incompletos">ERROR!!\nAll fields must be filled</string>
    <string name="bl4ko_des">BL4KO\n\nDj from Cordoba, co-founder of Roll in Bass who currently resides in Leeds (UK).\nSince he was young he has been influenced by the DnB movement, both nationally and internationally.  His main influences were Neurofunk and Jump Up and over time he submerged himself in sub-genres such as Deep, Tech-Step, Rollers or Liquid, which are reflected in his mixes.\n\nIt was in 2017 when he decided to enter this world, starting to mix at home as a hobby and DJing at private parties.\nLittle by little, it became a reality and in September 2019 he had the opportunity to perform at The Old Red Bus Station (Leeds), which has featured great artists from the English scene.\\n\\nNow he returns to Spain wanting to show everything he has learned and make it even bigger. "</string>
    <string name="coolbox_des">COOLBOX\n\nOne of the familys youngest.\n\nHis passion for D&amp;B begins at a young age, where the influence of his parents and the rave scene make him want to be part of this world since he was a kid.\nBeing welcomed by the wellknown Alharave collective, he begins to share his music in various events, parties and music festivals through the provinces of Malaga, Seville, and Granada: Industrial Copera, Paris15, El Tren, Palladium, Prisma, Cosmos , Sala Route 69, Quilombo, Red Zone, etc.\nThroughout his career, he has shared cabin with renowned bigname DJs such as DLR, Gerra &amp; Stone, Ill Truth, Data 3, Philth, LSB, Document One, Dj Limited, Levela, Black Barrel… His vision of D&amp;B takes him to her sets, always full of freshest and underground sounds from Rolling Deep, Jump up Rollers, Deep Rollers &amp; Jungle achieving an exquisite result. He also collaborates with other collectives like Zero2 Soul and Alharave promoting the scene and his taste for music.</string>
    <string name="acorn_des">ACORN\n\nWe are talking about a 24 year old young man from Madrid living in Malaga.\n\nHis first contact with electronic music was in 2012 with Breakbeat and its broken rhythms, but it was not until 2015 that his passion for D&amp;B and the beats of Neurofunk. Hand in hand with his musical maturity he began to have contact with Deep, Roller, Techstep. Its striking, dark and atmospheric sounds led him to fall in love with these styles, being reflected in the result of his sets.\n\nThis artists debut was in October 2018, and his little journey has passed through the well-known Paris15 and the familiar Route69. On his way, he has shared a booth with artists of international stature such as Teddy Killerz and Dub Elements.</string>
    <string name="blnk_des">BLNK\n\nThis young DJ from the Cadiz Mountains is passionate about hard drums and speedy rhythm. His style encompasses subgenres of Drum &amp; Bass like Techstep, Deep, Neuro and a Roller touch. His sets are always accompanied by reggae, jazz vocals,rap etc.\nHe has performed in various partys &amp; raves among Andalusia.\nIn Cádiz at Sala Holiday, Sala Pokoloco,Sala La Comedia (Jerez), in Seville in Sala Prisma and in Córdoba in Sala M100; also he has shared cabin with artists like Dub Elements.</string>
    <string name="elux_des">ELUX\n\nYoung guy from Malaga who started in the electronic music scene in 2010 with his broken rhythms.\nIt was then in 2014 when he met the D&amp;B thanks to the Rave clubs and events throughout Andalusia. Reaching its musical maturity, he begins to elaborate his first mixes just in 2019 under the aka ELUX, and that despite his brief experience in mixing, he contains a great selection and D&amp;B culture.\nA Roller vibes, strongly marked by a dark bass line and strong drums, together with the atmospheric touch of his selection, characterizes and gives the artist a unique identity.\n\nAbout his career, he has been fortunate to be able to take his music to the well-known Prisma Hall in Seville and various clubs and Rave events in Malaga and Granada.</string>
    <string name="gunpowder_des">GUNPOWDER\n\nWhen we talk about Gunpowder we are talking about a young man who started in the world of D&amp;B in 2016, where he began to attend various events, venues and festivals.\nHis love for the darkest and deepest lines was born discovering them in the underground scene.\n\nIt was in the Summer of 2019 when his first mixes were seen on cdj players and where he advanced at gigantic rates thanks to the help and support of his closest people.\nNow it is when the trend of his sessions will be recognized, showing his passion for Rollers and Deep within the D&amp;B, strongly characterized in his mixes where long mixes predominate, accompanied by double-drops and a serious and forceful line.\nAbout his experience, he has performed in various events and festivals in the province of Malaga, Granada, and in well-known clubs such as Sala Prisma in Seville.\n\nGunpowder also collaborates with other collectives such as the well-known Alharave, much loved by many of us.</string>
    <string name="minimaldrama_des">MINIMAL DRAMA\n\nThis artist From Córdoba, Roll in Bass member and one of itʼs cofounders, began to show an interest in D&amp;Bʼs roots from his continued contact with the Andalusian scene from 2015 and after with the underground British scene, where he was a resident for a long time.\n\nHe began to take his first steps in the world of mixing at various private parties in the UK, where he maintains close contact with British D&amp;B.\nHis style, where he likes to play between 172/175bpm, is clearly marked with Deep Minimal, Liquid, Tech Step, Rolling and Neurofunk, creating a dynamic atmosphere of strong bass, achieving a very personal result.</string>
    <string name="setelilak_des">SETE &amp; LILAK\n\nSete &amp; Lilak are a young spanish dj duo who also happen to be siblings.\nIn their hometown they have cautivated the ears of so many ravers over the past two years with their fast paced sets. They rush over the decks from the filthiest neurofunk to the deepest rollers also going through bouncing jump up and even some emotional dancefloor bangers.</string>
    <string name="rol97_des">ROLL97\n\nHe is a new upcoming artist in the scene of the Drum and Bass, born in Malaga (Spain) where he get that chill and liquid vibe and living in Bristol (UK) where he get that "Deep &amp; Rolling vibe", he has been working on his mixes for long time ago with a brilliant technique in the mix and mad skills on double drops and an excellent EQ of the tracks.\n\nAlso he started his productions one year ago with bid advances with forthcomings EP\'s in Tesseract Recordings(Yorkshire), Counterpoints Records(Portugal), Sixteen Step Records(Bristol), GhosBass Records(Sevilla), CST Records(Sevilla).\nRoll97 has played in events with artist like Octo Pi, Audiomission , Lupo ,Oto ,Incus , Nixxon ,Sam Harris, Master &amp;Disaster , Optimus ,Vandermou ,Sonar ,Adverse ,Mahza, Low Health.\nThis new artist will sound in the coming years and will be recognized for his dynamic drum games, accompanied by conversations between synthbass, and his marked funky rhythms that are hardly recognizable by very moving and vocal percussions that complete a perfect mix between Deep, Funky, Rolling and Liquid Drum and Bass.</string>
    <string name="sesion_activa">" The song is already playing"</string>
    <string name="reproducciendo_sesion">Playing song</string>
    <string name="sesion_detenida">Song stopped</string>
    <string name="no_sesion">It is not playing any song</string>
    <string name="sesion_pausada">Song paused</string>
    <string name="preparando_sesion">Preparing song, the play button will appear when available.</string>
    <string name="sesion_disponible">Song available, press play buttom to play the song</string>
    <string name="preparando_sesion2">Loading song</string>
    <string name="sesion_disponible2">Song ready, playing</string>
    <string name="sugerencia">Some suggestions? Contact us.</string>
    <string name="incluir_sugerencia">"Write here your suggestion. "</string>
    <string name="enviar">Send</string>
    <string name="sugerencia_enviada">Your suggestion has been sent</string>
    <string name="titulo">Tittle</string>
    <string name="sugerencia_existente">"There is already a suggestion with the same title. "</string>
</resources>